

# GOPIKA N A

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER

# **PROFILE**

I am a Software Engineer with holistic knowledge of backend development in python and implementation. I am also experienced in teaching programming languages.

- +91 8606361263
- in http://www.linkedin.com/in/gopikana
- Naduthadiyil(H), Vempally P.O, Kottayam, Kerala PIN:686633

### **PROJECTS**

### Paint Sales management system

- QR based system for managing paint company activities
- Backend Python, Django
- Frontend HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Database Mongo DB

#### **MTSS**

- managing admin side of banking services
- Backend Python, Django
- Frontend HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Database Mongo DB

### **Corporate Cards Platform**

- managing admin side of Corporate banks card service
- Backend Python, Django
- Frontend HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Database Mongo DB

## **SKILLS**

- Python , Django , Flask
- Html, CSS, Javascript
- Java, C, C++, PHP
- Teaching skills
- MongoDB, My Sql, Sqllite

#### **EDUCATION**

#### St.Stephens college, Uzhavoor

Msc. Computer Science | 2018 - 2020 CGPA : 2.99/4

# Mar Kuriakose Arts & Science college, Puthuveli

Bachelor Of Computer Application | 2015 - 2018 CGPA: 7.23/10

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Python Developer**

Ewire Softtech Pvt.Ltd | Nov 2021 - Present

Kerala Startup mission, Kalamssery, Kochi, Kerala

- Developing Web application back-end for managing admin side activities. The project used to manage bank customers. It has functionalities like customer onboarding using banking api's. It also includes reports, customer and partners ledger. The backend is mainly done in Flask frame work (Python)
- Python, django, Core-python, flask, javascript, java, Xml, AWS Basics, MongoDB, Mysql

#### **Python Trainer**

Logic Software Pvt.Ltd , Kottayam| Apr 2021 - Sep 2021

Kottayam

- Managed complex projects teaching from start to finish
- Collaborated with other developers
- Providing understandable examples for easy learning.